(Leonard:)How long have
you known Adam?
(Wil:)A few years.
Mm-hmm.
(Leonard:)And what are you
getting him back for?
(Adam:)Let's start with your
name and occupation.
(Sheldon:)Dr. Sheldon Cooper,
theoretical physicist, Caltech.
(Adam:)And what is your earliest memory
of the character Spock?
The first episode of Star Trek:
The Original Series I ever saw
was “The Galileo Seven.”
Uh, Spock had just landed
on the planet Taurus II.
Then my brother came in,
sat on my head,
and said, “Eat farts.”
After that day, I was hooked.
On Star Trek,
not my brother's
sphincter-based cuisine.
(Adam:)What was it about Spock
that appealed to you?
(Sheldon:)I think the same thing that
appeals to people everywhere,
(Sheldon:)the dream
of a cold, rational world
(Sheldon:)entirely without human emotion.
(Sheldon:)Spock came
(Sheldon:)from a planet governed
only by logic.